ladbrokes.be 2017-06-21

# Data Confidentiality and Management Policy - Ladbrokes Casino

The DERBY S.A. company, whose head office is established to the following address:  Chaussée de Wavre n° 1100, 1060 Brussels (Ouderghem), Belgium (phone: +32 2 349 16 11; fax: 02/349/16/15 ; e-mail: [info@ladbrokes.be](mailto:info@ladbrokes.be)) hereafter referred to as Ladbrokes.be ** _,_** publishes the web site [www.ladbrokes.be](http://www.ladbrokes.be/) and in that framework develops very stringent security measures aimed at protecting your data and your personal information against any unauthorised access attempt.

Ladbrokes.be protects your privacy and, as a result, acts in accordance with the provisions of the Belgian privacy law (Act dated 8 December 1992 relating to personal data protection). Please carefully read this confidentiality policy to find out more about how private data are collected and processed by our web site.

By using the web site [www.ladbrokes.be](http://www.ladbrokes.be/) , you formally agree to how Ladbrokes.be collects and processes private data, as described below.

__Confidential Information__

The information provided by players when they create their account is kept strictly personal and confidential. The information provided to Ladbrokes.be takes into account the full identity of the client, the age, the place of residence, the identification number from the national register, the occupation, the e-mail address as well as any other personal information provided upon the registration.

__Private data gathering__

Private data about you are collected in various ways through the use of the Ladbrokes.be site, including when you complete an on line form, when you subscribe for an information letter, when you play and if you use some on-line services to follow up on your payments.

In case you do not fill in one or several of the compulsory data emphasized in the form by means of an asterisk, you will not have the possibility, in some situations, to play or to receive the requested information.

__Processing and use of personal data__

Ladbrokes.be shall use the personal data from the player reasonably, and only to:

  * Allow him to play on their website
  * Proceed to payments and/or withdrawals
  * Enable the self-exclusion requested by the customer,
  * Provide them complementary information on the customer's request,
  * Optimise the functioning of the website.

However, e-mail addresses might also be used to:

  * Inform customers about new updates,
  * Send the information letters requested by the customer,
  * Inform the customer about the most recent promotions,
  * Allow the customer to proceed to operations such as deposits and/or withdrawals.

By providing such private data, you formally agree that Ladbrokes.be may retain and process such data for the above-mentioned purposes. 

These data are processed by Ladbrokes' computer specialists, (...!) and accountants. Each category of recipient only receives the data which are necessary to exercise their function.

Ladbrokes.be agrees not to provide your data to third parties, except for the banking or financial institutions that it cooperates with in the framework of its business on the [www.ladbrokes.be](http://www.ladbrokes.be/) web site and for the companies of the Ladbrokes Plc Group (shareholder of Derby S.A..), which will process them for the same purpose as above-mentioned.

Ladbrokes.be also has the right to share the private information they are in possession of, in particular the personal data and the betting history, with regulation or sports organisations or other, including the police in the case of an investigation on fraud, money laundering or sport integrity problems, in order to fulfil to their legal obligations.

Any automatic processing of private data is declared to the Privacy Protection Commission.

Upon subscribing the player may receive telephone or on line technical support. If a customer no longer wishes, later, to receive e.mails from us, he just has to write an e-mail asking to stop sending e-mails, to the following address : [help@ladbrokes.be ](mailto:help@ladbrokes.be)

__Amendment, rectification and deletion right__

The client may view his information and as needed, change or remove the same. To that end, he may send a request to the following address : [help@ladbrokes.be ](mailto:help@ladbrokes.be). The Client also has the right to object, free of charge, to the processing of his personal data for direct marketing. To that end, he may send a request to the following address : [help@ladbrokes.be](mailto:help@ladbrokes.be)

__Cookies__

Ladbrokes.be has the right to use cookies in order to better meet the specific requests of each player. Ladbrokes is thus able to better know the personal wishes of its users and thus customised the use of the site depending on each player's expectations. Cookies are also used to identify the favourite language of the holder of the account, for automatic selection when the holder of the account returns to Ladbrokes.be so as to check that the bests placed by the holder of the account are associated with his betting form and his account or to check that the holder of the account receives all possible bonus he is eligible for.

By surfing on this website, in spite of the warning about the cookies, you specifically accept the fact that Ladbrokes.be can use and store these cookies on your terminal.

You have the possibility to change the settings of your computer to be informed each time a cookie is created or to prevent their creation:

\- Internet Explorer : <http://windows.microsoft.com/fr-FR/windows7/Block-enable-or-allow-cookies>

\- Chrome : 

[http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=fr&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=fr&answer=95647)

\- Firefox : <http://support.mozilla.org/fr/kb/activer-desactiver-cookies>

\- Safari : <http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042>

Even so, accessing to our website will not be denied.

__Intellectual rights__

Ladbrokes.be enjoys protection of all its intellectual creations coming from, and found in, the web site. The protection extends to anything found on its web site, i.e. the data (or Data) such as contents, data, hyperlinks,,,,, quotations, slogans, statements, databanks, graphics, statistics, pictures, images, portraits, illustrations, drawings, logos, figurative brands, verbal brands, sounds, films, animation series, reproductions, ideas, concepts, patents, etc. Ladbrokes.be manages the rights relating to the data. All data is the property of Ladbrokes.be, except if the latter waives the same formally. Ladbrokes.be is allowed to change or delete or have changed or deleted the data unilaterally and at any time. In doing so it commits no fault and creates no precedent. To change, cancel or use data, ladbrokes.be may carry out an evaluation on a case by case basis. The visitor only has a strict licence to use the data (Data) in the framework of the normal use of the web site. The Visitor is not allowed to copy, distribute, adapt, transform, translate, etc. the data, for any other purpose, without the formal authorisation of ladbrokes.be and as needed, of the initial holder of the intellectual property rights. He should not place any hyperlink directing to the web site of ladbrokes.be or a ‘deep link' (the framing of a web site in another web site) without ladbrokes.be's prior and written agreement. The Visitor shall protect and compensate  ladbrokes.be for any infringement of the latter's rights or that of third parties (for instance copyrights, performing rights, rights relating to data banks, patent rights, the rights of the represented person to prevent the circulation of his image, …) that he may commit or inspire as needed.

Any supposed attempt aimed at unlawfully changing, damaging, abusively using or destroying the web site, the network, the data banks, the data, the software and/or the equipment, may be the subject of a complaint with relevant authorities and in court (police, prosecution department, …) filed by ladbrokes.be.
